[
    {
        "language":"Español",
        "questions":[{
            "question": "¿Cuál __ tu nombre?",
            "translation": "What is your name?",
            "answer":"es"
        },{
           "question": "¿Cómo __ tú? (informal)",
           "translation": "How are you?",
            "answer":"estás" 
        },{
            "question": "¿Cómo te __?",
            "translation": "What is your name?",
            "answer":"llamas"
        },{
            "question": "¿Cómo __ usted? (formal)",
            "translation":"How are you?",
            "answer":"está"
        },{
            "question": "¿ __ calor?",
            "translation":"Is it hot?",
            "answer":"Hace"
        }]
    },{
        "language":"Git Commands",
        "questions":[{
            "question": "How do you check your remotes?",
            "translation": "Google it perhaps...?",
            "answer":"git remote -v"
        },{
           "question": "How are new branches created?",
           "translation": "Check me out B!",
            "answer":"git checkout -b" 
        },{
            "question": "How are upstreams changed?",
            "translation": "https://stackoverflow.com/questions/2432764/change-the-uri-url-for-a-remote-git-repository",
            "answer":"git remote set-url origin"
        },{
            "question": "How do you starts the git process from commandLine",
            "translation":"Pretend the folder is already made.",
            "answer":"git init"
        },{
            "question": "Yes or no, is version control important?",
            "translation":"Think really hard",
            "answer":"yes"
        }]
    },{
        "language":"Français",
        "questions":[{
            "question": "Pardon ! ",
            "translation": "Google it perhaps...?",
            "answer":"git remote -v"
        },{
           "question": "__ m'appelle...",
           "translation": "My name is!",
            "answer":"Je" 
        },{
            "question": "Pouvez-vous __ ? (formal)",
            "translation": "Can you help me?",
            "answer":"m'aider"
        },{
            "question": "Je ne __ pas.",
            "translation":"I don't understand.",
            "answer":"comprends"
        },{
            "question": "Je vais bien ",
            "translation":"I'm fine/I'm well.",
            "answer":"vais"
        }]
    }

]